<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info xmlns:xsi= "http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://apps.nextcloud.com/schema/apps/info.xsd">
    <id>electronicsignatures</id>
    <name>Electronic Signatures</name>
    <summary>Accept electronic signatures on your documents.</summary>
    <description><![CDATA[# Features
- 🔒🔒 Accept Qualified Electronic Signatures (QES - strongest legal value) and Advanced Electronic Signatures (AdES) in PDF or .asice formats
- 🔒 Accept Simple Electronic Signatures (sms based signature - simple to sign)

### How it works:
1. Pick a file
2. Select "Signing" in the file's dropdown menu
3. Add signers
4. Signers receive a link on their e-mail
5. They sign the document
6. The signed document appears in your Nextcloud instance, next to the original file

# Built on top of eID Easy
Electronic signatures app uses [eID Easy](https://eideasy.com) as its signing back-end. eID Easy handles the signing process. Refer to [eID Easy's pricing](https://eideasy.com/pricing/) for pricing information.

# Three levels of electronic signatures
**Qualified Electronic Signature** - A Qualified Electronic Signature (QES) is the most secure and legally recognized form of digital signature. It’s equivalent to a handwritten signature in the European Union and can replace paper-based signatures in most legal contexts.
QES ensures the highest level of security with strict identity verification, multi-factor authentication, and compliance with international standards, making it the ideal choice for businesses needing legally binding, tamper-proof digital signatures.

**Advanced Electronic Signature** – An Advanced Electronic Signature (AdES) offers higher security and legal validity than a Simple Electronic Signature (SES), without the complexity of a Qualified Electronic Signature (QES). It uniquely identifies the signer, ensures they control the signing process, and guarantees the signed data hasn’t been tampered with.

**Simple Electronic Signature** - A Simple Electronic Signature is any form of digital consent or agreement that links a person to a document or message. It is the most accessible and widely used type of eSignature.


# Pricing

Every business is different — [talk to our experts](https://www.eideasy.com/book-a-call) to get a custom quote based on your location, use case, and volume.
Whether you're serving one country or many, we offer flexible pricing that aligns with your compliance needs, usage volume, and geographic coverage.

# Feedback is welcome
eID Easy connects your business to [80+ identity methods](https://www.eideasy.com/supported-methods), Qualified Trust Service Providers (QTSPs), and Certificate Authorities worldwide — all through a single, secure API.
If you’re not seeing your preferred method, let us know at info@eideasy.com.

# Documentation

## Set up
See the following guides:

1. [Installation](https://docs.eideasy.com/nextcloud/nextcloud-app-installation.html#_1-installation)

2. [Set up](https://docs.eideasy.com/nextcloud/nextcloud-app-setup.html#_2-set-up)

3. [Signing a document](https://docs.eideasy.com/nextcloud/nextcloud-app-signing.html#_3-signing-a-document)


[CHANGELOG](https://github.com/eideasy/nextcloud-electronic-signatures-plugin/blob/master/CHANGELOG.md)

]]></description>
    <screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/eideasy/nextcloud-electronic-signatures-plugin/master/img/screenshots/screenshot-1.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/eideasy/nextcloud-electronic-signatures-plugin/master/img/screenshots/screenshot-2.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/eideasy/nextcloud-electronic-signatures-plugin/master/img/screenshots/screenshot-3.png</screenshot>
    <version>3.0.6</version>
    <licence>agpl</licence>
    <author mail="info@eideasy.com" homepage="https://eideasy.com">eID Easy</author>
    <namespace>ElectronicSignatures</namespace>
    <category>files</category>
    <category>integration</category>
    <category>office</category>
    <bugs>https://github.com/eideasy/nextcloud-electronic-signatures-plugin/issues</bugs>
    <dependencies>
        <php min-version="8.1"/>
        <nextcloud min-version="31" max-version="32"/>
    </dependencies>
    <settings>
        <admin-section>OCA\ElectronicSignatures\Settings\AdminSection</admin-section>
        <admin>OCA\ElectronicSignatures\Settings\Admin</admin>
    </settings>
    <activity>
        <providers>
            <provider>OCA\ElectronicSignatures\Activity\ActivityProvider</provider>
        </providers>
    </activity>
</info>
